Entrepreneurially-minded, resourceful and driven creative problem solver with 7+ years experience as an operational leader in early-stage. Oxford science MA (Hons) and Quantic MBA (Hons). Smart generalist and excellent people manager with experience working in international teams and across multiple operational functions utilising technical, creative and analytical skills. Intellectually curious, highly organised and detail-oriented; excels at process improvement and efficiency. Selected (1% acc. rate) to join the NEF Fast Track 2020 scheme, which develops and supports the entrepreneurial leaders of the future. Winner of the NEF Fast Track 2020 CEO's Award and winner of the 2020 CVC Young Innovator Awards. Growth mindset with a unique approach as well as a diverse and rare skill set that brings significant value to any business Maxx works with.

## **CROSS-FUNCTIONAL STARTUP LEADER**

- Operations
- Strategy
- People / HR
- Projects / Events

- Mgt Accounting
- Startup Legals
- Digital Marketing
- Front End Web

### **EXPERIENCE**



Startbook

Products and services for entrepreneurship programmes

Founder Jul 2020 - present

London, UK

• Won two pitch competitions, a grant of £20,000 and doubled revenue from Year 1 to Year 2.



Kantan

Tech platform for trade professionals to manage and execute work

**Founder Associate** 

Aug 2019 - Oct 2020

London, UK

• Placement role as part of NEF Fast Track scheme. Have taken on a variety of roles including operations, software engineering, quality assurance, business development and special projects



Self-employed

Startup consultancy providing strategic and operational support

**Startup Consultant** 

Feb 2018 - Jul 2019

Remote

- Acquired multiple clients by understanding problem areas, pitching solutions and negotiating contracts
- Continuously worked with 1 client for over a year, helping her launch her new book, websites and startup
- Increased Instagram following >1000% by expanding knowledge in photography and digital marketing



The Family

Pan-European startup network, service provider and shareholder

Head of Events (London)

Nov 2018 - Apr 2019

London, UK

- Worked closely with C-level entrepreneurs to create educational and entertaining content for 13 events
- Organised a biotech enterprise innovation conference featuring 10 senior life sciences speakers
- Sourced over 1000 emails and managed a targeted cold email campaign to advertise the conference



**Invisible Technologies** 

Worldwide on-demand virtual assistant platform and service

**Director of Operations (Contract)** 

May 2018 - Aug 2018

Remote

- Successfully managed a global team of 50 people (5 direct reports) across numerous time zones by employing strong management skills
- Increased operational efficiency by 30% and client billable time to 1400+ hours of direct labour per month by introducing new revenue streams and improving load balancing across teams
- Improved client experience as measured by qualitative feedback by supervising quality and providing constructive feedback to operators



### **DWYL**

Web app development agency and coworking space

Co-founder & COO

Jan 2017 - Dec 2017

London, UK

- Significantly strengthened brand position with minimal cost (£250) by enforcing trade mark rights to acquire highly valuable 4-letter .com and .co.uk domains as well as social media marketing handles
- Improved efficiency of financial administration by 300% by creating and implementing an automated contractor invoicing system
- Delighted clients and successfully managed numerous projects by employing strong communication and project management skills



## **Hack Partners**

RailTech innovation accelerator, hackathon and consultancy

**Founding Partner** 

Jul 2016 - Jan 2017

London, UK

- Promoted to partner status after 3 months due to competence, diligence, zealousness and significant contributions to the business
- Contributed to pivoting the business model in a new direction by evaluating customer feedback and working closely with the founders
- Bolstered the closure of several major partnership deals collectively worth over £100,000 by communicating and working with senior stakeholders across the industry

**Head of Operations** 

Apr 2016 - Jan 2017

London, UK

- Managed accelerator programme featuring 11 tech startups, organised a 300-person conference and 120-person hackathon featuring senior stakeholders from across industry by employing strong project management skills
- Successfully acquired Tier 2 license and joined Tier 5 intern scheme allowing the sponsorship of 2 international candidates without professional legal advice by thoroughly researching guidance and executing the process with detail
- Managed creation of a legal procurement framework for startup-TOC software and hardware trials by assessing the contract landscape and working closely with a law firm



## **Entrepreneur First**

Deep tech company builder and venture capital fund

**Operations Manager** 

Sep 2015 - Mar 2016

London, UK

- Diligently managed investment operations for 33 startups on the programme by using strong organisational
- Successfully managed over 30 visa applications including Tier 1 Entrepreneur and Tier 1 Exceptional Talent by utilising strong project management skills and detail-oriented nature
- Organised and ran several high-profile events including a 300-person Demo Day attended by top investors by using strong organisation and event management skills



## **University of Oxford Department of Widening Access**

Widening access academic summer school programme

**UNIQ Operations Manager** 

Jul 2013 - Aug 2015

Oxford, UK

**UNIQ Academic Mentor** 

Jul 2012 - Jul 2013

Oxford, UK

- Managed college sites with teams of 4 staff and 50 residential students by using strong management skills
- Successfully resolved a number of sensitive incidents requiring pastoral care by using empathetic **communication** and knowledge of child safeguarding
- Increased competitive applications from state school students to the university by encouragement, mentoring students about the university's application processes and the academic content of the courses

## **EDUCATION**

C	entre	
TOP	preneurs	5

**Centre for Entrepreneurs** 

Foundation supporting entrepreneurial talent (1% acc. rate)

**NEF Fast Track 2020 Fellow** 

Sep 2019 - Aug 2020

London, UK

Highly-selective learning programme that supports participants in launching a startup by providing a startup work placement, support network, executive coach and business mentor



#### Quantic

Elite online remote MBA programme (6% acc. rate)

MBA (Hons)

Feb 2018 - Nov 2018 Remote

2 projects and 8 concentrations:

Accounting

Marketing & Pricing

- Accounting project
- Data & Decisions
- Finance

- Marketing project
- Leading Organisations

Markets & Economies

Strategy & Innovation

Supply Chain & Operations



**Udacity Google Scholarship** 

Mobile Web Specialist Nanodegree Challenge (5% acc. rate)

Mobile Web Specialist Scholar

Oct 2017 - Feb 2018

Remote

Offline First • Service Workers • Caching • ES2015 • Destructuring • Promises • Proxies



**Founders and Coders** 

Highly-selective 8-week web development course

Full Stack JavaScript Web Dev

Jan 2015 - Mar 2015

London, UK

HTML • CSS • JavaScript • Git • GitHub • Jekyll • Markdown • APIs • Node • Hapi • D3



# University of Oxford St Edmund Hall

Ranked #1 academic institution for biomedical sciences in 2011

MA (Hons)

Cell and Systems Biology

Oct 2011 - Jun 2015

Oxford, UK

Major: Cardiovascular, Renal and Respiratory Biology Minor: Cellular Physiology and Pharmacology

**Project:** Varying enzymatic digestion to improve pancreatic islet isolation yield and clinical outcomes for type-1 diabetes

ousu	Oxford University Student Union	Student representation for communication with the university		
CODES UNVESTE ESTROY SWOM	MedSci Division Representative	Oct 2013 – Jun 2014	Oxford, UK	
OXFORD UNIVERSITY SPORT	Oxford University Sport	University sports society and dodgeball club (OUDbC)		
	Founder & President (OUDbC)	Mar 2013 - May 2014	Oxford, UK	
	Finance Executive	Mar 2013 - Mar 2014	Oxford, UK	
$\sim$	Oxford Entrepreneurs	Events and programmes supporting er	ntrepreneurship in Oxford	
œ	Oxford Entrepreneurs  Executive Committee	Events and programmes supporting er Oct 2013 - Mar 2014	ntrepreneurship in Oxford Oxford, UK	
œ	·	, , , , ,	Oxford, UK	
OU.S. F.M.S.	Executive Committee	Oct 2013 - Mar 2014	Oxford, UK	